xvidupdate.com 2011-11-23

# Watch HD Movies Online

Privacy Policy

We take complete care of your privacy as we know how important it is for you. We have some created some privacy clauses where you can see how we collect, communicate, disclose and use your personal information. The clauses are:

  * When you are asked for your personal information we make sure that we know the reason for which the information is collected.
  * The personal information that we have collected we will use it to fulfill the objective for which the information was collected unless we have the consent of the client or law.
  * We will save the personal information until is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which we have collected it.
  * The information will be collected by lawful and fair means, and of course with the consent and awareness of the individual.
  * The personal information is very important for the fulfillment of the purposes that is why the personal data should be the complete, accurate and up-to-date.
  * The personal information will be protected from loss, theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use and modification.
  * The information about our policies and practices related to the management of the persona information will be available for our customers. 

We are committed to work according these clauses in order to make sure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected.

xvidupdate.com is distributing a modified installer which is different from the original ones. The modified installer is compliant with the original software manufacturer's policies/t&c's. Additional software may be recommended to users on a opt-in basis during the installation.Copyright © 2011 xvidupdate.com. All rights reserved.
